♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
[Atoy] If there's another gate there,
it's surely locked too.
What will we do?
[Atoy] If there's a lock,
that means there's a key.
[Ibyang] What is your mission?
Let me join!
[Ivan] Is this what you're looking for?
We can talk about this.
- [gunshot]
- [groans]
PREVIOUSLY
[Ame] I told you to stay
with Emerson, right?
Let me join, Sister Ame.
What exactly are we supposed to do?
[Ame] What we need to do is get
Samir's cellphone or wallet.
Don't let the captives out!
[gunshots]
[shrieks]
[in English] I will kill you.
[grunts]
[in English] Where is my brother?!
[Samir, in English] In hell!
Would you like to say hello?
[grunts and groans]
- [Ivan] Don't kill him! We need him alive!
- [gunshots]
[grunts, growls, and groans]
- [in English] Only pepper, no spray!
- [pained grunt]
[Artem, in English]
You can do everything you want to him,
but your Atoy remains our prisoner.
What will we do now?
Looks like we're at a dead end.
There's another way.
[Uno] I'll call our boss to consult him.
[suave theme music playing]
[music fades]
[ominous music playing]
- [gunshots]
- [groans]
[foreboding music playing]
- [music fades]
- [suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[phone keypad beeping]
[line ringing]
[in English] Bad news.
Samir has escaped.
[tires screeching]
[suspicious music playing]
[speaking in Russian] What happened, boss?
[in English] I was attacked.
[in English] You're attacked?
[in English] Identities?
[in English] Friends of Atoy.
[in English] I'm glad you're safe, sir.
[in English] Anyways, I have news for you.
[in English] Our prisoners almost escaped.
[in English] Boss, I said almost!
[in English] They are back in the cell
and are being punished.
- Should we report to the ambassador?
- [In Russian] Never!
[heavy music playing]
[in English] We must find his family,
right now.
[in English] Yes, sir.
[music swells, fades]
[pensive music playing]
Audrey, how are you?
I can't sleep.
I don't know anymore
how this mess in our lives will end.
I'm restless, Ame.
I know I need to be strong, but…
it's hard.
But I can't give up now.
[melancholic music playing]
We're with you, Audrey.
We'll help each other so we can find Atoy.
Hmm?
So, how's your foot?
It's okay now. I can move it.
[Ame chuckles softly]
Oh, by the way.
We saw Ibyang earlier.
She asked us to give this to you.
She said you'll understand it.
[sentimental music playing]
Oh, sorry. That's probably lukewarm now.
You've already done so much for me.
You even brought me soft food.
[chuckles softly]
I just asked my sisters to buy that.
You even baked for me!
- Isn't that harder?
- [laughs]
[chuckles]
[sobs and chuckles]
Is the taste that bad?
This porridge is perfect, Ibyang.
[inhales] I was just
wishful thinking that…
[sobs] I hope…
I hope my child is as kind as you.
She remembers you
even if you're far apart,
and even if she's already with her mother.
Ibyang is really sweet, isn't she?
She still remembers me.
[chuckles softly]
[gentle music playing]
Does she know that
her Tatoy is missing?
[sighs] We didn't tell her.
I don't want to ruin
her bonding with Olga.
This is actually the first time
they're together, just the two of them.
Hmm. If I tell her what happened
to Atoy, she'll worry.
[melancholic music playing]
Okay. Charmi, we're about to go out now.
Ibyang, come on.
Where are we going?
I'll explain it to you later. Huh?
[suspicious music playing]
- Uh, good morning, ma'am!
- Oh. Hello, hello.
- Uh, ma'am, may I ask something?
- Ah, yes.
Where is Olga's house?
Oh, are you the ones my friend said
who would collect the debt?
[henchman 1] That's us. She sent us here.
Oh, yes! Yes, brother.
Hello. Good morning, brother!
She's been waiting for you
since yesterday.
- What's--
- Shh.
She left last night
because she had a taping.
She'll be gone for three days.
Just come back another day.
[softly] Just between us.
We came from such a far place.
What do we do, miss?
Well, what can I do?
You won't be able to get anything.
You won't be able to collect anything.
Just come back another day.
- Mmm. Okay, okay. All right, we'll leave.
- Okay! Okay.
[Charmi] You can pass through there.
- [Charmi] All right.
- [phone keypad beeping]
[phone ringing]
[tense music playing]
[Charmi] Friend.
You owe me.
There were three men here, collecting.
But you know me.
That script of ours is automatic.
I already handled it.
What debt? You're unbelievable.
You're putting me and Ibyang in danger!
Huh? Why?
Those three men you talked to,
they're enemies!
What's wrong with you?
Call the police now.
Or-- Or the village police.
Or any of our backup!
Oh-- No, no, no. Okay. No, they're gone!
- They're still here.
- [gasps]
Friend, you're wrong. They're still here!
- There, look!
- [Charmi] Sorry, sorry, sorry!
Sorry, sis!
- Friend, I'm sorry. They're still here!
- [indistinct]
[gasps] Ibyang! Come, come, come!
[panicked gasping]
Here, here, here! Here! [panicked gasping]
[in English] Oh my God. [gasping]
Come on. [gasping]
Wait, wait. Here, here!
Go inside. Get in here, quick!
- [music fades]
- [loud sigh]
[in English] I can't reach him again.
He won't answer anymore.
Your son decided yesterday.
Most likely, he won't talk to us.
I just want to know if he's safe,
or where he went!
[mysterious music playing]
Where would Audrey go? To Atoy, of course!
Do you know where he lives?
Not yet, but that's easy.
Send our people to Tabang Lupa.
Let them observe there.
But keep a low profile.
[Martina] When you see them,
don't ever hurt my son.
And make sure you bring Audrey
and Janine here immediately.
[in English] Okay?
Oh? What are you waiting for? Go!
- Let's go!
- Go, go.
Anyway,
our men who are looking for Olga
and Ibyang have already reported to me.
They're at Olga's house now,
and hopefully by lunchtime,
we'll have Ibyang.
- [suspicious music playing]
- [in English] Finally, some good news.
[music fades]
Not here.
Check upstairs.
- Come.
- [in English] Yes, boss.
[ominous music playing]
[gasps, hushes]
[whispers] Don't make noise.
[clattering]
[gasping]
[suspicious music playing]
[henchman 1] What? Are they there?
[henchman 2] Not here!
Check under their bed! They're just there!
They can't escape inside this house!
[henchman 2] All right!
[henchman 1] They're just hiding!
Open those doors!
[rousing music playing]
- [spritzing]
- [screaming]
Ibyang! Come on, hurry!
Come on, come on! Hurry, hurry!
[gasps] Ibyang!
- [grunts]
- Wait!
What?!
- [grunts] Let me go!
- [rousing music playing]
[in English] Dmitri is dead,
and his daughter, Audrey, is missing.
[in English] We need
that woman and her daughter!
[in English] Or that man will not talk!
[in English] We don't need them
with us to make him talk.
[in English] What are you trying to say?
[in English] We only need to make
him believe that we have his family.
[in English] And how
are we going to do that?
[in English] With this.
[in English] This was recorded
in the interrogation room
after the break-in
at the ambassador's office.
[suspicious music playing]
- [device blips]
- [Samir, in English] Start with your name.
[in English] I am Audrey Regalia,
the daughter of Dmitri Regalia.
[in English] Please tell me what happened
in the ambassador's office.
[in English] Well, the ambassador
was showing us his office
when he noticed
that there was a chair out of place.
[in English] When he looked behind it,
he saw there was a hole in the wall.
[in English] Window, sorry.
[in English] And then, a guy in a mask
jumped over the kitchen counter,
hit my dad and the ambassador
over the head,
and climbed out of the window.
[in English] And you do not know this man?
[in English] No! He was wearing a mask…
[in English] And how is this
supposed to help us?
[man, in English] With the help of AI.
We can mimic the woman's voice,
and we can make her say anything we want.
[in English] Okay. Do it.
[in English] Do it now.
[music fades]
[grunting and groaning]
- [clangs]
- [groans]
[groans]
- Ibyang! Come on.
- [henchman groaning]
Mama! [squeals]
[gasps]
- [grunting and groaning]
- [squealing]
[gasping]
[indistinct chatter]
[grunts and groans]
You two, out!
- Hurry! Oh!
- Quick, quick, quick!
Oh, oh! No one make the wrong move!
Move! Go there! Hurry!
Hurry up! Don't be slow,
and don't you da--
Oh! What? One wrong move,
I'll put holes in your bodies.
Oh!
[scoffs] Oh! Ay! [gasps]
[squeals]
[Charmi] I'll report you! Don't--
[Charmi grunt, squeals]
[Charmi] Friend, run now, friend!
The gun is fake.
Quick, run now!
We'll hide here! Here, here.
Lie down, lie down, lie down! Duck, duck!
[groans]
Did you see those three women
who came out?
- [in English] Listen.
- [music fades]
[Audrey gasps, in English] Please!
[in English] What do you want from us?!
Whatever it is, just spare my daughter!
Don't take her, please! Have mercy!
[in English] What--
What did you do to them?
[pensive music playing]
[in English] They are safe.
[in English] A little hurt,
but they are safe.
[in English] So now that I have
your Audrey and your precious daughter,
who will protect them from men like me?
[in English] All right! All right.
[in English] I'll tell you where it is.
[in English] I will tell you
where the laptop is.
[in English] Just don't do
anything bad to them.
[in English] You better tell me the truth.
[in English] Yes. [sighs]
[music fades]
They ran there!
They said there. Come on!
Come on!
[somber music playing]
Brother, where are they?
Just stay there.
The bastards might come back.
Yes, they might come back.
[panicked gasping] Friend, it's okay now.
Come on, it's okay now.
- They're gone.
- Okay?
[pensive music playing]
Friend, we need to leave
because we still have somewhere to go.
[panicked breathing]
Good thing you arrived.
Where are we really going?
We're going to Atoy.
He needs to know something.
[Olga] O-Okay, Mars.
[stammers] Can you just call him?
He's not answering!
Go now, leave!
- The two men might come back, hurry!
- Okay, okay.
- Come on, quick. Run, run!
- [indistinct]
- Quick! Sis, thank you!
- [groans]
[music fades]
Atoy.
They have your wife and child.
[suspicious music playing]
That means they'll take my child next.
Don't worry.
They won't hurt you.
You're still useful to them.
[sighs]
We need to get out of here again.
But how? Didn't we already try?
We don't even know which hell we're in.
[tense music playing]
[man 1] Next is the car and the tractor.
We're inside a junkyard compound.
We need to know the exact location.
But there's something
you need to know about Janine.
[heavy breathing]
She's not your real child.
[pensive music playing]
[knocks on door]
- [Ame] Audrey.
- [door squeaks open]
Um…
Do you want some breakfast?
No.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
You look like you didn't sleep.
I dreamt of Dad.
I found out that
he was buried this morning.
I didn't even get to visit him.
It's just sad that…
we ended up like this.
[sighs] So toxic.
[Ame] Your situation is very pitiful.
I'm sorry.
But it's really good you survived
such a chaotic family.
Ame.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Even this child got dragged in.
She'll be even more hurt
when she learns the truth.
- [Ame] The truth?
- [pensive music playing]
Before we escaped…
my dad told me…
Janine is not my real child.
- [music intensifies]
- What?
Are you sure?
[sniffles]
I don't think he would lie anymore.
Ame, let's keep this between us, please.
I need to talk to Atoy first.
Then, together we'll tell Janine
the truth.
My brother's sin is truly horrible.
So many people got involved,
so many people got hurt.
[in English] Dad, those poor girls.
Even his own child.
And especially Janine.
Did you ask who your real child is?
[music fades]
I still don't know.
[melodramatic music playing]
But wherever she is…
I hope I still get to know her.
[music fades]
[epic music playing]
The court has released
a warrant of arrest for former
Mayor Rizaldo Coloma,
the alleged bagman of corrupt senators…
[Emerson] Here we go again.
Here's that crocodile again.
He never does anything else,
except steal and steal.
I'm so furious-- so furious at him.
- I've had enough.
- This is who Atoy should be looking for.
…spotted in Vietnam
and still being pursued by authorities.
Oh.
Enough of that news.
[Cita] We already have
so much to think about,
and that news just ruins the day.
This is what
I'm really thinking about, miss.
[Emerson] How will they catch
this bastard?
- [Emerson] It won't work again.
- What?
- [Emerson] It's not--
- I already turned it off.
[Emerson] The remote isn't working.
[Emerson] There are batteries.
[Emerson] Oh, that's why.
Oh.
- Hey. Ibyang!
- Sister Ame!
- Hmm. I missed you.
- [Emerson gasps]
[in English] My love, my love.
[soft chuckle]
[Emerson, in English] My love.
[happy sigh]
Ame, can you please take Ibyang
to your room first?
Why?
- [Cita] Uh…
- [music fades]
Uh, Ame, Ibyang's back is wet.
Go on. Change her first, Ame.
[Cita] She still has clothes
upstairs, right?
- [Ame] Uh, yes.
- [Cita] Go on.
[Emerson] Go on, go on, go on, go on.
Change her now.
When she says it, do it right away!
Change her shirt, Ame.
You really should. [huffs]
- Right, my love?
- [sneaky music playing]
Good day. I am Olga.
- Ah, Olga.
- Um…
[in English] My future ex-girlfriend.
Uh, Olga, what happened?
Why did Ame have to take the child away?
Is there a problem?
[sighs] It seems so.
[sighs] I've been calling Atoy
for a while.
He's not answering.
Oh, he hasn't come back yet.
Uh, uh…
My love, what are you going to tell Atoy?
You can tell me. I'll understand.
[rousing music playing]
It's…
Atoy is Ibyang's real father.
[tense music playing]
[electronic blipping]
[Lily, in English] Sir, please.
Have mercy.
[grunts]
[in English] No, no, no, no!
Stop, stop, stop!
[in English] I will give you
what you want!
[in English] I will tell you
where the lap--
[groans]
[man, in English] Samir, that's enough.
[in English] And what will we do with him?
UP NEXT
OMG, Miss C!
Aren't Ibyang and Janine the same age?
[Cita] Oh?
Oh, then maybe Ibyang
is also Audrey's child.
Audrey needs to know this.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Ibyang?
Ibyang. Ibyang, this is Atoy.
Tatoy?!
[in English] What are you doing?
Who are you talking to?
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
‪Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias